miucolor.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - MIU COLOR

MIU COLOR believes in protecting the privacy of our customers. MIU COLOR wants you to know how we collect, use, share and protect information about you online. By interacting with us, you consent to our use of information that is collected or submitted as we describe in our privacy policy. We may change or add to this privacy policy, so we urge you to review it periodically.

  * WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED
  * HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED
  * HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION SHARED
  * HOW TO REMOVE YOUR NAME FROM OUR MAILING, SHARING OR EMAIL LIST
  * SECURITY
  * UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

### WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED

#### Types of personal information we collect include:

  * Your name"
  * Your mailing address"
  * Your e-mail address"
  * Your phone (or mobile) number"
  * Your credit/debit card number"
  * Your purchase/return/exchange information"
  * Your wish list information"
  * Your date of birth or age"
  * Your location"

If you choose not to provide personal information, we may not be able to provide you with requested products, services or information.

#### Automated Information Collection

We may automatically collect non-personally identifiable information about your hardware devices (i.e., your computer or mobile device) when you access the MIU COLOR Services. For example, when you visit miucolor.com (the “Site”), we may collect your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer or mobile device whenever you access the Internet, as well as information about the type of Web browser software you use and the referring Web site. This number does not identify your name, email address, or other personal information. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our service and to administer the Site. We also collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of cookies. Cookies are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our websites and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. We use them in order to remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites. You may decline to accept cookies by modifying your Web browser settings. MIU COLOR, its advertisers and ad servers, including without limitation Google and other third-party companies, may also use cookies, as well as files called "Web beacons" or "clear gifs" to determine on an anonymous basis which advertisements and promotions our users have seen and how users responded to them. However, we do not use these technologies to collect personally identifiable information. 

### HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION USED

Examples of how we use the information we collect include (but are not limited to):

#### Product and Service Fulfillment

  * Fulfill and manage purchases, orders, payments, returns/exchanges, or requests for information about our products and services in our website, or Amazon shop, or to otherwise serve you.
  * Connect with MIU COLOR regarding customer service via our customer service center, or on social media platforms.
  * Provide services such as Wish Lists.
  * Administer sweepstakes and contests.
  * Notify you of any products you have purchased that are subject to recall or withdrawal.

#### Our Marketing Purposes

  * Deliver promotional offers, coupons, mobile coupons, e-mails, mobile messages, and social media notifications.
  * Provide interactive features of the website or mobile applications, such as product reviews or marketing communications and other information regarding products, services and promotions.
  * Administer promotions, surveys, and focus groups.
  * Use a review you submit for commercial purposes to promote the products or services in your review. We may also include the user name and city/state you gave when submitting your review.

### HOW IS YOUR INFORMATION SHARED

We may share your personal information in the following ways:

We may share your information with our service providers who manage our customer information and perform services on our behalf, such as fulfilling promotions, sending communications to our customers, conducting surveys, etc. We do not authorize any of these service providers to make any other use or disclosure of your information.

We may share your name and postal address with our reputable retail partners so they may send you catalogs about our products and other products of potential interest. We do not share credit card information or email address with these third parties. If you prefer that we not share your name and postal address with other companies, please see “How to remove your name from our mailing, sharing or email list” section below.

### HOW TO REMOVE YOUR NAME FROM OUR MAILING, SHARING OR EMAIL LIST

You may choose to receive or decline communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You also may use the following options for removing your information from our database so as not to receive future communications, or to no longer receive our service, or to not share your name and address with other companies. 

  * You may send an email by clicking [**here**](mailto:marketing@miucolor.com).
  * In commercial emails that we send you, you may use the “opt out” or “unsubscribe” option included in the footer of the email itself.

### SECURITY

Company incorporates reasonable safeguards to help protect and secure your personal information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, or wireless transmission, or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that Company cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Company via its Web Sites, and you do so at your own risk.

### UPDATES TO THIS POLICY

If we intend to use or disclose your personal information in any way materially different than what we say in this privacy policy or make any other material changes, we will make reasonable efforts to revise this policy. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the “Revised” date below.

Revised April 2016
